singaporewritersfestival.com 2013-05-08

# SWF 2012: Privacy Policy

|  |  | PRIVACY POLICY  
---  
| Singapore Writers Festival, National Arts Council (NAC)'s priority is to maintain your trust and confidence when handling personal information about you. |  |   
---|---|---  
|   
---  
Information Collection and Use  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) collects personal information when you register with Singapore Writers Festival (NAC), when you visit Singapore Writers Festival pages or the pages of certain Singapore Writers Festival partners, and when you enter promotions or contests. Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners.  
When you register we ask for information such as your name, NRIC/passport numbers, nationality, birth date, gender, mailing address, contact numbers and email address.  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) does not share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies.  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Singapore Writers Festival cookies information, and the page you request.  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) uses information for the following general purposes: to update news/information, fulfil your requests, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous statistical analysis report for internal and external use.  
Information Sharing and Disclosure  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) does not share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide information you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) under confidentiality agreements. Under direction from Singapore Writers Festival (NAC), these companies may communicate with you about promotions, contests or offers from Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to use or share this information.  
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to violations of Singapore Writers Festival (NAC)'s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
We transfer information about you if Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) may notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.  
|  |   
---  
Cookies  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) may set and access Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) cookies on your computer.  
The third parties' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Singapore Writers Festival (NAC)'s cookies.  
Confidentiality and Security  
We protect this information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet applicable law.  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide updates or news to you or in order to do their jobs.  
We train our employees in the proper handling of personal information. When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the confidentiality of personal information they receive.  
Photographs  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) commissions a photographer each edition to take pictures of the Festival. Some of the pictures will be used on this website, in print or other broadcast and online media to promote Singapore Writers Festival (NAC). Please contact us if you believe a picture should not be used for any valid reason.  
Changes to this Privacy Policy  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending notice to the email address specified in your Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.  
Copyright and Intellectual Properties  
Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users to do the same. Material available on or through other web sites may be protected by copyright and the intellectual property laws Singapore.  
It is Singapore Writers Festival (NAC)'s policy, in appropriate circumstances and at its discretion, to disable and/or terminate the accounts of users who may infringe or repeatedly infringe the copyrights or other intellectual property rights of Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) and/or others.  
http://www.singaporewritersfestival.com and its related websites will never share your information, including your e-mail address and mobile phone number, without your explicit permission.  
| DISCLAIMER  
---  
|  | Ownership  
---  
This website is the property of Singapore Writers Festival, National Arts Council (NAC).  
Use of Information and Materials  
Any unauthorized reproduction, disclosure or distribution of copies by any person of any portion of this website may be a violation of the Copyright Law. It may only be reproduced, disclosed or distributed for non-commercial use with written authorization from Singapore Writers Festival (NAC).  
Links  
This site may contain links to website controlled or offered by third parties [non-affiliates of Singapore Writers Festival (NAC)]. Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) hereby disclaim liability for, any information, materials, products and services posted or offered at any of the third party sites linked to this website.  
By creating a link to a third party website, Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) do not endorse or recommend any products or services offered or information contained at those websites, nor shall Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) be liable for any failure or products or services offered or advertised at those sites. Such third party may have a privacy policy different from that of Singapore Writers Festival (NAC).  
|  | No Warranty  
---  
With all the material contained in these web pages, Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) has attempted to offer the most accurate and up-to-date information possible and thereby does not warrant the accuracy, adequacy or completeness of this information and is not liable for errors or omissions in this information. Singapore Writers Festival (NAC) reserves the right to discontinue, or change at any information in these web pages without notice or liabilities.
